Hello. Oh. Is that too loud? Let me
know. Turn it. Turn it down a little.
Wait, is my mixer showing?
Hello. Welcome to the night.
I have been editing some live stream thoughts.
I'm getting a hang of where the audio should
uh live at, so to speak, for both a game and then
going to get my Windows on my desktop. All
when I unplug my desktop or my TV
or anything, windows get moved.
Got a new packet.
I need to actually
turn off Windows sounds.
Keep a close eye on the volumes today for Kingdom Hearts because Kingdom Hearts. Loud. Uh they didn't
add volume controls. Correct me if I'm wrong. They
didn't add volume controls till the PC version.
Okay, that hot key. I know the captioner
always says hotkey. Hockey. Hot key. It
doesn't know the word hotkey.
Okay, there we go. I got it.
All right, disembark.
Uhoh.
That isn't good.
If I absolutely can't save, I'll just
not save. I guess it's that simple.
Cuz how save states work on
our the PS3 emulator is it
actually stops the game to continue it later.
doesn't let you keep playing. At least not
at the moment. That's not how it works.
I I need to organize OBS a little bit
better. I can't find things sometimes.
Boy, they I know I could just not save
just in case it does happen again,
But, Kingdom Hearts isn't the kind of game you want to do that with.
You could lose progress real easily if you do that.
Oh, cross your fingers.
I don't want to save over the one we have already.
Oh, it worked. It It worked. It worked.
That was a fluke error. I don't know
why that happened. Maybe it's because I
copied it from a different configuration.
Something big's supposed to happen.
And now allow me to introduce the master of
terror, the king of nightmares, Jack Skellington.
Bravo, Jack. Bravo. Those ghosts will
be a big hit at this year's Halloween.
Thank you. Thank you. But their movement
still needs work. It's not scary enough.
I want to strike bone-chilling terror.
I'm going to consult the doctor.
Then I'll go attend to the decorations.
Really odd entrance way here. Like
the smallest room in the game.
I don't understand. Maybe the guidance system was
damaged in the explosion. Nonsense. My devices
are always perfect. Oh, I've got it. Why, of
course. The Heartless need a heart. Doctor,
do you think we can add a heart to that
device? Certainly. A heart's not all that
complicated. Let's get to work. To make a
heart, first take a container with a lock.
We need the key to this thing first!
That's, uh, Rob Paulsen. Jess Harnell?
I think it's Rob Paulsen because he does voice in Birth By Sleep
I don't know Finkelstein
Not really.
My! That was amazing. Uh, and you are
Sora. Well done, Sora. I'd like you to
be a part of this year's Halloween. What's this
Heartless doing here? Oh, the Heartless came
to town just recently. What's frustrating
is I can't get them to dance with me. So,
the doctor and I are trying to improve the
guidance system. He's quite a genius. Okay,
doctor. Let's continue. The ingredients
for a heart. Pulse. Emotion. Terror.
Fear, hope, and despair. Mix them
all together, and we have a heart.
It failed.
Maybe we're missing some
ingredients. Let's try adding memory.
Sally! Sally! Good-for-nothing girl. Don't know
why I bothered creating her. Sally's got the
memory we need. See if you can track her down. No
problem. Sora, would you like to come along? Sure.
Jack! Jack! We have a major crisis. The Heartless
are completely out of control. We can't stop them.
Hmm... Maybe our experiment triggered
something. Everything will be fine,
Mayor. You have nothing to worry about.
Take that!
Come on!
C'mon!
>> Come on
Hurricane Blast
Check out our new abilities if we have any
Can't.
Have an AP Up?
Defense Up.
You usually always check to see who
has the lowest event. Give it to them.
Got a torn page back there.
I'm going to skip even though we're doing a a uh trophy uh run, this time around
I'm going to skip Winnie the Pooh
world because, Hundred Acre Wood, even if we could
Even if we wanted to, you know. I don't think
it's the most fun Winnie the Pooh world. So,
we're going to skip this. We might do the special
the secret bosses at the end of the the series,
though. I think that'd be fun to see cuz this
is a low-level sort of run kind of so that be fun
and I probably alluded to alluded to it
but I've never done the uh unknown fight
except for level 99 Sora so it was really
easy so I'd like to see what it's like
When you're underleveled.
I'm not I don't even have an idea of how the
fight goes really properly because I
just annihilated uh Unknown Figure.
Yeah, I kind of want to take
off slapshot for a hurricane,
but we need more AP. Hurricane spin was it
uh I'm going to adjust my game.
Game's kind of loud in my ears.
Thunder. Thunder.
There we go.
The sound card thing
It's Zero. I didn't get to see you in the other game.
Zero! Have you seen Sally anywhere?
Is something wrong, Jack?
>> I like the.
No, everything's going great.
We're going to have the best Halloween ever.
>> I'd like to play it if I have time still
All we need now is your memory.
"Memory"? You mean this?
I haven't even played Luigi's Mansion 3 yet.
I got to set some time aside
Jack, I have a bad feeling about this.
Why don't you try something else? There's still time
Nothing could beat what I've got planned.
Once we get the Heartless a Heart,
they'll dance just as I envision it.
Trust me, you're going to love it.
Hurricane Blast.
Hopefully we uh get either level
up with for AP or get a AP up.
This is how far the series has come. You
really cannot change your party members
out unless you have a save point.
You'll know that Kingdom Hearts 2,
you could change it anywhere long as
I think you can even do it in battle.
Rock. Yeah. Barrel. Did you hear that? Yeah,
I sure did. A heart. What should we do? Gosh,
you really are stupid. Isn't it
obvious? Tell Oogie Boogie. Probably
not. That doesn't make much sense
to be able to do it during battle.
I do want to see more of the Nightmare
Before Christmas abuse revenge game. No,
I'll probably I need to set aside some time. Today
is the 30th now. By the way, tonight is daylight
savings time, so at some point we will uh have a
time change. Maybe during stream. I'm not planning
on doing anything other than Nightmare Before
Christmas World tonight. So, yeah.
Another fix. Where's the Where's Where's the babbie?
Where's the little guy?
There he is.
They're just misunderstood. Not bad. Thunder-era. Thundara. That's a gummi ship laser.
We still need We still need to actually change
our gummy ship for final gummy ship uh routes.
Go back to the doctor. The doctor.
Doctor. Doctor. That's
where we're going this time.
A heart? That bonehead jack is really
making a heart? I'll be jigggered. That
works for me. Ohh, when I get my hands
on that. Well, I've got no hands,
but I'm still going to nab that
heart and control the Heartless. [laughter]
Find the mayor. He's at the um guillotine gate.
We have some artless. Uh, we'll
skip that. We'll skip him this time.
No, actually, he's in a different location.
That's where he shows up when you bleed the world.
Got to kill him here though, otherwise we
can't uh use our reaction command thingy,
which originally reaction commands weren't
on triangle for this game. They were on
um main menu, you know, the main command menu
the attack I believe prompt that was changed.
There are a lot of differences. PS2
forget about like camera controls,
right? Wait,
the animation is real quick.
Maybe too quick. The game freeze.
Save often.
remember that. I wasn't expecting that to happen.
This is That's a little frustrating, is it? Uh,
can I switch it?
Oops. All problems, I guess tonight
Okay, I got to reboot the the
game yet again. Yet again.
This time I'll make sure to save. We were
right at the guillotine gate, too. We should've saved.
save. Glad I know that. That particular
trigger uh that that scene change, freeze the game.
Not really.
Uh, Jack know any magic healing?
Jack's basically another mage.
Heal us. More of a black mage.
Graveyard.
>> Come on.
Got on some experience here.
Check this place out too once the Heartless are out of the way.
Search light ghosts, uh, matter
That only lost only lost like five or ten.
Do you have to talk to the professor, doctor.
Skip doing that. Fade out. Probably probably.
Ah yes. Yeah yeah yeah.
Oogie cutscene
Yes, in terms of the Oogie's Revenge game,
I still haven't got
Basically I got as far as the YouTube video that we did
I haven't got any further than that.
I haven't played until uh
last weekend. No, yesterday. Yesterday.
Kill these Heartless,
and then make sure not to let the game freeze on us, huh.
I really wish, it would be great if they did have
the savestates working
for all intenses, correctly
'Cause then I could do that, uh
use it as safety precaution
'cause it's a lot easier to do that than find a save point.
Just in case, I'm going to
go ahead and go back and save
Good. It should work this bad.
Suppose it's not not a bad idea if I explain every
episode of this series.
We're doing the PS3 games so I can get the trophies,
but we're emulating it so we can have 60
fps, which wasn't a thing on the PS3 game.
And in case you're if you're curious, yes,
that'll work because the last stream of this
series, we'll do it on an actual console using
the same save file. We'll still get the
trophy unlocks at the end of the game. Um,
I haven't tested that because that's a whole 15
hours to go through. I don't want to do that.
"Check the tombstones."
Memorization game
♪ Doo-d-doo doo, dooo!
What happened?
Oh, that happened. Exploding pumpkins.
Is that a thing that Joker does from Batman?
Why does that sound familar? Exploding pumpkins.
I'm done here. Could have sworn there's more view
or am I thinking of a different room?
There's two exits here. Uh was
this an entrance or an exit?
One goes one way, go one goes
another way. I did it again.
Good thing we saved. See, that's why I did it.
Sorry if I was a bit quiet in comparison to the uh music
guys. Don't kill all the zombies
for me, Jack. I appreciate it.
The search ghost really fit the
level here. Not so much Monstro.
Guess they're like a parasite in that
case. If you want to if you want to really
be creative
The jingle jingle
bojangle, nonsense
I almost got that wrong. Okay,
That should have been longer, Mayor
To be honest. Played a little
bit more of a game with me.
This goes to the uh gravestones.
Correct. That's where we want to go.
Then we can go to the doctor. Dr. Finkelstein.
There are a few secret chests in that area.
I'll try to get them. Might be helpful.
There you go. This time it's sure to work.
there. Those little fool guns stealing my work.
Those seem to be working for OogieOogie Boogie.
They're probably at Oogie's place right now.
Kids took off with the heart.
We lost them.
Zero. After them quick.
What you going to do?
Ghost dogs have teeth?
You know, I remember having
this questioning myself who
it was really called Pumpkin Hill before.
What kind of appreciator of
Nightmare for Christmas am I?
I can't even name all the locations of the film.
To be fair, they don't ever say it in the film, right
Gonna choose to believe that "Curly Hill" doesn't sound great, so it's not what it's called
I say appreciator cuz I'm not a big fan.
I'm not a fan anyone Disney property
orator. I I I do like most of Pixar's work though,
but not enough to actually keep up with
them. One of the first times he can't
control a camera here. Most games would show a
camera with an X on it. You goes to the hill.
Stronger the attack, the more tech points
you get, the more difficult it is to block.
Do that on a Shadow, you'd only get one.
Thanks for lighting the fire, Jack.
Save me some MP.
Jack-O'-Lanterns don't do
anything other than explode though
They might give you magic [?]
Have to. No, we could just keep going. There's a Trinity down there.
Think it's a white one, so we can't do it. I
would be wary of any way of freezing the game.
Okay, it is actually uh on access
and we can kill everything.
Here I come. That's not what I wanted to do.
Here I come. Dead.
I might have actually been correct because I
don't know if you can examine that
when there's enemies on the field.
Technicality, I am still correct.
Believe it or not, we're
already going to Boogie's Manor.
Oh, well, that was the right idea.
I'll get Donald in here.
Boss fight.
Come on. Come on. There actually a shortcut
here that'll get us back to the uh plaza.
Dead things up there. He dead still.
For puppies, probably. Nope. No puppies.
Flare-G. I don't I don't know what that is
Might be a cannon actually.
as the guys in the Ugies revenge game said
or risk doing it again. Not
want to risk doing it again.
That technically comes from
the fountain somehow. Shortcut
to do this.
That low attack power.
Sora really taking its toll. I want to kill things.
I want you to be uh gone.
You're already dead. Undead.
Undead. Don't know what that means.
How could something be undead?
Do this thrice or something nice.
more than thrice. Come on,
Jack. Thought you liked rhymes.
Get to actually see inside of Jack's house.
Inside of Jack's home in the revenge game.
That's real nice.
This isn't nice is I have
to kill everything probably.
I see the uh menus pump can't do anything.
Guys are called Wight Knights. I
don't even know what the word "wight" means.
W I G H T heard that word except for this game.
Come on. And these are of
course gargoyles. Come on.
Actually acted as if they were gargoyless here.
One.
So, we didn't take it. So, there's no platform to
ride. Two ways you can get back into this place.
Here I come. You can't. That is so evil.
At least I don't have to trigger all the
fights here. Get rid of the guys
that aggroed us or aggroed on us.
I did not see um
Can skip here though.
Should actually just be skipping it. They say
something. I knew Okie Boogie was behind this. FPS
won't break. And if
Okay, normally I would just fall off
here and get everything below us.
There might be stuff down there. We're just
going to go beline for the door
here. Can't open it right now.
Not the right move here.
Oh, Square knew exactly what they were doing.
The flying guys here. They want
you to fall off. Ok, where now
over there
Nope. We didn't fall off really
action.
See how poor I am at killing
things? Very slow at it.
We're not even the the last world yet. Oh well,
more experience is good. How do I get back up?
Come on. Don't want to I don't want to fight you.
Well, I guess I have to jump off to go back up.
I know. nonsensical, right?
Can I ride you?
Go away, you lose— durn
Oh
Oh, thanks, guys.
Runaway bathtub
There's going to be another one.
See, we don't have Donald.
They didn't bring back trinities in
the other games. Even though you can
switch your party members
at any time out of battle,
I was just too late to switching.
I knew that would do something.
Oh, brother.
I've had a a bit of a roller coaster
weekend. Been a bit of a bit of a
wreck. I don't even know where I'm going
now. Where where where are we going next?
Can't remember. Was it the uh
hill again?
I like goofy leveled up a long time ago.
Yikes. Oh, nervous.
Picking bathtub
crash the game. Thank you. I guess it is
evil. Evil bathtub, right?
Thank you, Goofy. Going to swap
out for Donald while we're here.
Shouldn't have to fight anything again. We know
this. All right. Right game.
I'm going to go and change.
Oh my god. Yeah. Wait, you know what? These are
actually in this situation a
bit faster. I would reckon.
Have that on my quick select. Stop spinning.
Even know what to use on you. Arrow. Oh.
spending to do uh to paint dominance.
Good. Bye-bye. Goodbye. Now
Oh, it's the other mushroom. Uh, I'll show them
off a little bit. If you attack them too many
times, get poisoned. Also, you attack them too
many times, they use that to become invincible
for a short amount of time.
I'm not sure if there's a trick to killing
these guys to get special items or not. Couldn't
tell you to be honest.
Area is pretty as
a blow these up.
I knew Oogie Boogie was behind this.
Not fall off this time
See, it was a good idea to change
our quick select fire lizards.
So easy. Got the ether I use back. Nice.
Where are these? Fire. This fire powered
camera.
Fire. Get out of my road, Gargoyle. Fire. See you.
that dove in Apu-style to save its friend.
Thunder. I guess the gargoyle is not white
knights. Come on. The other kind of white knight.
It's a shortcut. I don't want to use that, but
you can't use it, I think, in battle. They uh
wouldn't it be funny if I shrunk there and crashed
the game? I actually didn't have it enabled.
Another chest.
Without glide though
Hey, kill these bad guys and let me open the chest.
I can't fall off here. fire. You
know, with how my week's gone,
I should probably not say stuff because it
might the opposite might end up happening.
Not a very good cage if we can't jump off here.
Not very safe
This place is, not very safe at all.
Oogie Boogie we're talking about here.
That one we can't get yet. You definitely
can't get to that one quite yet. Okay,
the door will go through us to the boss. A mini
boss. Bye-bye, white knight. Have a nice fall.
This is how eerie. How creepy. How bizarre.
They can just teleport as they fall off.
I have to leave the camera on.
I got to go take get up here.
Sure. Notice chat message. Yeah, I don't
have timestamps on these chat messages.
I wonder if I can enable that. That
would also enable it on the overlay.
I don't want to see that. 4 days for
first. Yeah, I I guess November is
having a new month happen. It's
always refreshing. He's staring.
Sorry I missed your message
It does have a uh time stamp on
the website. a little bit ago,
then
can't think of what would be in two two days.
Check on Sonic's Sonic Frontiers. It's coming out
uh November 8th and so is God of War Ragnarok.
Anything on first? once.
All right, side the mansion now.
Chasing down these little brats kids causing
trouble and following down these claws
for all that.
I know exactly why I would miss messages on YouTube, because
this window was... overlapping the chat. I could fix that though.
Handy hot key to set some boys on top.
Very useful. Just type of thing to use it.
Oop!
No voice acting. Yeah, they don't say much in this game.
I think they've said their own dialogue here.
Can you name the three kids?
>> You're in for it now.
Lock, Shock, and Barrel. I think Barrel is the short guy.
Shock.
I'm gonna say Shock is the red devil guy
>> I'll behave, I promise
What are you saying, kid? Fire.
I surrender!
Sorry.
Looking at it here, you have lock,
shock, and barrel lined up. Probably
the girls lock. You think I'd memorize
that because they they announced theelves?
I did not get it memorized. Seen the movie like
four times now. I have any I don't have a memory.
So, I I think the plan is I want to just sit down,
play some games, watch some movies before stream,
but it's going to be a stream tomorrow
featuring another skeleton dude.
Tonight we had skeleton Jack the Pumpkin King
tomorrow. We're going to have Sir Daniel
Portiscu in Medieval for the PlayStation
4. That'll be fun. I want to continue my save
file that I have for that. Uh I think I left off
I want to say the antill.
There is a level of ant hills
in it. I think that's where I
left off at a quarter through the
game. I think third or quarter go.
What lever? Pull the lever. Crump.
This lever?
You don't have the heart. Spooky has
it. There's no way I'm going to let
you There's no way I'm going to let
you take you to him. Take you to him.
Did that figure he has to? What's he
going to do with the heart? Eats me.
Kind of a bully to Barrel, aren't I?
Poor kid. He's the guy He's the kid that
just goes along with his friends like
because no one else will
I guess no one else will hang out with him or
supposed to be trick-or-treaters. Uh, attack it.
That's where they have all their traps and stuff.
I saved.