GoodYes yes.
I'm kind of stuck here aren't I I really
don't think there's anything I can do other
than restarting
Jeez Louise
Ridiculous
The butcher we need to find The ButcheryOver
that might be it.
That's why I'm going to call it
Here it is.
No sign on that so this just regular house
okay
Believe we need that to go in there
anyway.
I haven't been out here yet
They are faster than me almost
Even the big guy
Here it is
This should be it. Sack.
Back 'bout
Like a meat a meat house
You don't want to go in there quite yet. I might
get my ass handed to me
Okay now I'm ready
More danger upstairs.
Away from the barrels so I can
Perfect.
Okay I don't need... Can I get in
61. I haven't killed anyone yet
Doot doot doot doot dooooo
That was the blacksmith because the guy was
renowned for making busts, which of
one of which we have
But I don't think we would go there because
it's already it's already made so
Skip...
...The rope. They're like machines so they
don't add to the Chalice right. Do they?
Are they enchanted? They are, okay.
Made with, uh, magic. Dark magic from,
What's-his-face
Chaos Rune. I bet the Chaos Rune is outside the village.
Gonna wager a guess that's where it's at
I would think a hammer's good on these
Throwing daggers and crossbow.
It's not going to work well an armor.
Down here
Library
So interesting
And now I get hit.
Hit by the butcher. Great.
All of that: No no.
I do not want. *scoff*
Especially the dragon toads.
Oop. Back to the, church.
That's where the blacksmith comes in
I think I'll skip reading anything else I'll
come back later on my own time
Get these bones rolling
How do I get outside the village? That door's shut already?
I saw an exit
But we need something to make and we have the...
We already have stuff to make it with
A furnace thing.
Perhaps not
Using it
Need to do more
If I could just melt the statue I already have
I can get gold for the,
Crucifix.
Maybe I need to combine them? Like do them—
There's‒ this must be the gateway I need to go through
Oh, it's over here
Explore some more
"I see you!"
[continued accent]
Gonna lay ya out with one blow, I am!
'hop you right in half with my axe!
Wa‒ ter
Ah...
Something underwater.
Nothin- nothing here quite yet. I think,
Maybe the Shadow Rune will. Something here. I don't
know.
[with accent]
When I get mah hands on him
It's a roof tile or something on top of
that awning
OK, what do I do here?
That's a pretty color for the...
where...? Oh, it changes~
[chuckling] Holiday cookies
A way to open the gate
Oh was there something in there?
There was a, uh
That's stained glass, I thought there was a potion
Something else glowy
Is all
[exhaling]
Maybe I'm supposed to read
I didn't want to read.
That's the exit, I persume
head
Like Chernabog
Reading it is
The books do stay open
I'll put this in the right order when I edit this
I'm going backwards
Doesn't appreciate the finer arts of reading
And if you recall, I think all that was
probably spurred on by his dead puppy
Shame that.
As a child he got into alchemy, is... *hmpf*
Probably! I don't know.
Well that is obviously not it. There is no
lore-driven gameplay here.
Where do I go next
I am wondering I will try to figure it out
on my own though
Libraries done
I keep on seeing "Trolls Head".
Don't know what that means. Like a tavern?
Door I haven't went through yet.
Is this, that's just the house. Yeah.
I can't go underwater that is a certainty
Nothing outside; that pond is not where we need to
go
Out of my way please. Thank you.
You're... Just fine
You-you're fine
I mean,
Not really, you're kind of possessed right
now, but
We'll‒ I'll take care of that. Sir Daniel Fortesque will.
There... I think we just need to go to the.
There... I think we just need to go to the. Blacksmith.
Must be missing something.
As usual I am missing something
We just have a cast so we can't go to the
-That- area
Not going to do us any good
Need an actual, Crucifix
Maybe this really is like Bugs Bunny & Taz;
maybe I have to jump on this a lot more than I was.
The light changing in here, or is that just my
imagination
Boy speedrunning this level must be fun
I thought there would be some sort of
indication but
Indeed. Could be.
Ohh!
You have to do it in front
And melt the gold down
Again - in front of the forge.
To be fair it does prompt me what to do here
I just wasn't seeing it
Ta-daaaa!
Banish all evil
Except for the big, mech guys
Well, almost.
Well, almost. You'd think that would do something.
I guess that's cool
Heh heh heh heh‒
Are we going to do something... unsmart here
But like I know these Shadow Demons.
I think I've seen them before in gameplay
OK I'll be right back. Not going to leave this,
room, here, in case I end up getting...
Destroyed by something that appears now that we've done this
Heidi ho
Let's-a go
Ah, we looped around here
The other side of this gate now.
Goods around here?
There's the Chalice
A potion.
do do
Gate from this side now
They do drop gold
One gold
I'll buy so much with that one piece of gold
Get in through the roof...
Ah! Probably.
[Looks] like a vault
We will unleash heck
upon the Earth.
Probably
Soon, soon - eventually we will. This is just the shadow...
have a key for
"No safe is safe."
Especially this one
chateau artifact
Chateau.
Is this a chateau, a shadow chateau? Cuz it's a
house?
Seems to have no other significance
Okay I got to go bash some.
Mechancial heads in and we can get the...
Chalice
Oh did the gate open?
How convenient. How convenient, thank you gate.
Must have been linked to the switch
100% per-cent. Percent
Avoid the dragon toads. Do not touch them.
We go right, for the witch
There's multiple paths to go down. I think we'll will go with the
There's multiple paths to go down. I think we'll will go with the, the ant tunnels first?
Ope‒ that's, that's not good!
That is one path we do *not* want to go down.
Wrong book. Wrong
Wrong book. Wrong thing.
I like the fairies are following us here,
ones we've rescued.
It's very easy to toggle off the HUD
It's mapped to the
L3 button.
Setting for the 30 FPS didn't persist, but pretty sure it's usually 30 FPS anyway on a regular PlayStation 4, so...
We're doing two things down here, one of which we just completed
Got enough amber for the witch.
I know what that means!
[And] me without a shield
Look at the pretty fairies
I believe this level was pretty notorious back in the day
For being hard to get through.
Looks much better in this version though
I feel like that's the case.
Solder ants here
Oh dear
Not too sure if I'm just bad at this game, or if it's really difficult
Little bit of column A, little bit of column B.
Bows here aren't really going to help us because they're so fast, these ants
They stay on us very easily
Feel like our strategy of just using a sword's probably for the best
If I die again we'll go back and refill our health a little bit more if I can, if I can do that.
"Thank you for releasing me."
Oh really? You're doing that, doing the thank you for releasing me thing
You know what you're doing, fairy
You know what time your game came out in
Yeah it was a lot darker in the PS1 version.
That, I know of.
Open ze chest.
I've already been live long enough to be‒
This stream has been longer than the last one.
[Of] this game.
A lot of enemies here
Almost like the hit boxes on these ants
are too short to hit with the stronger attack
Did we just go in circles?
Well that's easy to do in these
Labyrinth-like tunnels. Jeez.
That's one thing they kept true to the
original game. Confusing.
I had enough trouble in the village!
I'm not going to bother with strong attacks
I'm not going to bother with strong attacks.
They don't seem to connect.
Oh you have a jump attack as Dan, too
You have some sort of jump attack, it's more of a stab.
Be good to know
Have a lot of sort of fossilized remains down here
Seen some ammonites
Trilobites... Amber of course
The hammer does deal more damage
Two hits versus three
Unless the sword might be enchanted sometimes that would be, when you want to use it.
I started off with it,
I started off with it, being a good idea
We're getting through this a little bit better now
The sword is faster, though
You keep on using your hammer, you're going to be open to attacks more
These guys… Probably a good idea not to be open to attacks, they're very fast.
Like I've found a way forward without too much
trouble
Ah, we're being overachievers now are we?
This is very pretty
I don't like, what
I don't like that though, that looks ominous
I could tell when there's a boss up ahead
The telltale signs of something dangerous
How wonderful.
ooh
[repelled]
ooh.
Hmm, yeah there's there's an ant somewhere here.
And I don't have a shield. This is not going to be…
Clean. This is not going to be clean, I bet.
At least I have an enchanted sword now
Got a weak point, or a charge up attack? Okay.
OK I probably want a ranged weapon -this- time around
Actually it's both: A weak spot and it's charging its a charge up
Why don't you crush the ants
Yeah!!
"Antagonist"! [chuckle]
That went better than expected I almost died. I came, I came within the
That went better than expected I almost died. I came, I came within the range of dying, but uh
Let's deal with this guy rather.
Jesus
so's the aforementioned dying
Fortunately they give us some health, or is, is that that a teleport
I think that's an exit
Am I stuck down here though, I feel like I missed a...
I am stuck down here.
A victorious retreat
You fairies can be saved next time.
Now that's going to be helpful
we'll find out what it is
once we go to a new level.
I think we'll just go ahead and go
let's explore the enchanted grounds a little bit more
If I can get to it
There we go.
The enchanted grounds, The Enchanted Earth. Soil.
"Detritus"?
detritus
Is that a word, detritus?
I don't know how to say that
That's too big of a word for me to actually pronounce correctly.
That's too big of a word for me to actually pronounce correctly. Too smart.
I shall retreat.
What are you doing…
Dan is that a chicken?
Pull out a chicken
Pulled out an emergency chicken.  For some reason.
If I if I if I,
Take myself out will I get health back or
will I just respawn almost dead again
Let's find out!
"Shadow Demons"…
Is this linked to the, we need the shadow
yeah that's the, the Shadow Artifact will let us get the Shadow Demons opened.
The Tomb of the Shadows, if you will
"Tomb of the Ancients", yeah.
Nice, Rayman...
*I* didn't set the chicken drumstick to anything, it just appeared
Embrace the toads
Emergency life bottle
The very least I'll get a full health bar.
Wouldn't leave me with nothing would you
It left me with nothing.
This is the, uh
This is "Dark Souls" before Dark Souls was a
thing
Where is an easy to get to fountain
I suppose Cemetery... Return to the Graveyard?
Actually I just think, uh
The Graveyard would be it
Actually multiple ones there, being the first level and all
So what did I do over my month break of streaming - from streaming?
I played some more Crash Team Racing Nitro-Fueled
Get some pit stop progress, didn't...
unlocked a few things, one new character
Nothing too exciting though
I got a, a single Velo time trial, in Coco
Park - one of the easiest tracks in the game.
First Velo time trial ghost I beat.
OK, so there should be easy to get fountain and also easy to avoid enemies right
Won't be dying anytime soon here
Can't catch me some zombs.
Can't catch me some zombs. Zombles
There, money
I will take that again.
Why do I have a chicken drumstick again? What is with the chicken?
Oh you do have a charge shot, cool
There's one more fountain in this area
I believe
Unless the graveyard does get split up and I'm thinking of that level
Rune
Here we are
Hello I am back
Where we going next
We're gonna explore more of The Enchanted Earth
Without being
Susceptible to death
That's noooo good
Chat I don't find myself...
Chat I don't find myself very commonly in this situation,
but what do you do when there's a cat that wants your attention and you're trying to play a game?
Do you ignore the cat?
So I see the captions aren't working
But I am talking, and it's coming through,
Sooo, let's reset that
Let's reset that and it get working
Should be better okay that's better
So those ants that we killed in the tunnels down there
They didn't count towards the Chalice, so that's technically a separate level entirely
But we definitely have stuff to do here because we have a Shadow
...Artifact
What did the witch give us? Let's find out
What did we get from the witch?
We get anything good?
Did... She give me a chicken drumstick? Is that why I had that equipped?
That is hilarious.
Why.
It's so useless
What am I supposed to do with that
Ok
What's more economical the crossbow or the longbow
'Course we can get the witch summoned again if we want
If we want to go down there but I don't want to do that anymore.
Too claustrophobic down there
I don't I think I'd rather go with the bow here
The game seems to do that a lot
Get something new, the old weapon just kind of becomes,
Get something new the old weapon just kind of becomes pointless to use.
Oh if you run out of ammo then there'd be a good reason to go—
None shall pass!
Ah that's probably the
Probably related to the artifact huh -
guardians keeping us out.
Where does this go?
Nowhere.
A golden dragon egg
That's where we got the Witch's
That's where we got the Witch's Talisman,
Cemetery Hill.
A small detail I thought I heard there
Must have been Sir Dan's armor
Clanking around
Going in here yet? Course not.
Guess we do need to go up to the treetops
And I'll go ahead and tell you right now the the
goblet-
What's this thing called? The goblet
What what... the uh, the uh
The drinky thingy, you want to kill the Shadow Demons to fill it this time
everything else doesn't do any good
Our health is full.
Our health is full. Nearly.
Might as well be.
Oh did I find some treasure
Oh that's very hidden
Go on the other side
Hey kind of
Not really
I feel like I'm quiet again in terms of comparing it to the game's
Turn it down a bit
I've been keeping an eye on it
How quickly am I going to get attacked by things
These are dragon eggs and they're going to be dragons, right
What a cool level
A nest. What was noise?
Talons
Look at the book entry, here
Get a trophy for all this stuff
Get a trophy for all this stuff. Probably.
Dragon Bird
The boyd
"She's not just a set of legs - there's" … Play the narration
Hold on a second. This text is kind of small
So I'm going to go back and actually enable the game subtitles for the stream
[Didn't] realize it was so small
Let me help you out there with that
[laughs]
Be gone, beast!
Dis-gus-tang!, Disgusting beast, get out of here
She is gone, actually, she is dead.
We took care of the Queen Ant
I have some questions though. How does the narrator know what an airlock is
Isn't this supposed to be the Medieval times?
What else could it be other than a space
A spacecraft
Where am?
Okay probably not the best idea for a sword to be used here
Do I get a target if I switch to my bow
I mean it's listed as a boss in the Book of Gallowmere, so I assume we do defeat it
Even though the eggs are what we're coming up here for all right
Oh there we go
Gold for that.
Gold for that. Oh she's gonna be maaad.
Okay I guess no defeating you
Mama bird.
I just leave you,
I'm sure, I'm sure you'll have more babies at some point
Distressed. I'll leave her distressed, and unhappy with me.
I thought there would be more to it, but I guess that's it.
I mean I did get money from that, can't argue with that
Shield
This has like Zelda energy, it's like I get a shield but it's useless. what.
Literally I already had a shield so
No point in collecting it. I guess I could come back and get it.
Again that's going back to what I said before
it can pay off to know where all the collectibles and the healing spots are in the game
You can go back and prep yourself I guess; they do come back.
Wrong door. It's not the right door.
What am I shooting at
Why's there a gargoyle behind a gate
What is the point of that
Shadows
...Why do I want to do this again?
Leave now or share their doom. Okay!
I'll leave. Heheh
I'll leave.
I knew I'd drown there, I knew that was a deep pool of water
Not safe not safe.
[exhausted sigh]
Yep, I'm leavin'
Gonna go away from that.
Clearly there's something that goes here
To stop these lasers.
You know it wouldn't be the first time I've taken a game too literally
The first time I played Zelda: Breath of the Wild I didn't talk to Impa
The entire game, until
I decided, okay I probably missed something I was like oh I am ready I guess I guess you were just...
I took them too seriously and I was like "Okay. I'm probably not ready."
"This might not be a good thing"
That's one way you can play the game,
Just explore it and not focus on the story stuff.
All it was was the memories; you unlock the ability to regain Link's memories.
I think Impa put that a little bit too high up on this seriousness level if you ask me
I'm only going to go somewhere else because I have somewhere else to go
If I need to come, if I need to go back there - fine, I will. But let's just go to the hedge maze here
Asylum Grounds. This is a pretty fun level I think. From what I could, from what I've seen.
At least, it looks cool. I don't know if it's irritating.
Why does that keep happening
Darn gates!
These hinges are too...
These hinges are too... Well,
These hinges are too... Well-maintained.
These hinges are too... Well-maintained. They just
close on their own.
Oh dear
[slight panic]
Case in point - my shield is already gone
Y'know, if it weren't everything in this game being so...
Oh, you want to kill me.
Exactly. It's kind of cute looking isn't it?
It is the cutest thing I've seen in this game.
In a strange sort of way
Are you Jack?
Are you Jack? Big statue guy
Riddles are not my strong suit
And more friendlies here to listen
About
That's not uh
Rats, they are the rats.
Heh heh heh heh…
The Rat King.
The Rat King. Where have I heard that before?
Mmm, brisket
You actually get— no, that's the, the Shadow Beasts
Seems like part of a puzzle to me
Not the one we're doing now though
Oh. Yeah, ok...
X marks the spot huh
Okay that's definitely a wall I can break down right
Surely that one will be broken
Oh, no
Get back here!
I need you for my Chalice
Stars?
Stars are something that don't show up during the day.
I need to hear that one more time
Stars -would- match that description
But who steals stars?
Why would you say that
Like what else would the topriaries be for right?
Topriary
There we go
Doing the thing with the captioner again.
Bad at pronouncing things.
I'll solve this like I solve any other puzzle!
Wandering around until I figure it out.
Stars are it.
Yep. That's it.
He want me to…
Slash up all the star topiaries
Chaos Rune needed
Chaos Rune needed. This gate.
Are there two sides to this place
Oh here's one.
Nope. They gotta be over here.
What is that out there, a mansion?
Hm. We'll find out some day.
Is that a squid?
What the heck
What the
Cthulhu is that
I'm beginning to wonder if some of these walls aren't breakable
Shall just try breaking all the walls
Oh there's a face‒ there's faces, in this walls.
These are the hedges of evil.
These are the hedges of evil. Truly.
Fish.
Cross.
X-mark.
Is that a freaking camel
This place is weird man
ope. new way
'k…
Hmm
Need a faster weapon
a *faster* weapon
Almost have it
It doesn't appear to be timed
It's just a matter of being faster
Or, it *does* appear to be timed. There's no, uh
Puzzle here
Yeah, ah.
Yeah, ah. Hmm.
Yeah, ah. Hmm. Interesting
Getting so close
Let it reset here
I'm feeling like there's something up here, because I don't have a way to refill my ammo that easily
I can hit them all at the same time, that would be one way of doing it
Hm...
I think the crossbow is the way to go
I can't see anything
I can't see Jack
Behind the wall, like that.
But I will go see Jack.
In case I need to do that first
Yes yes.
Get our equipment back up
nah I think we're good with the sword for those guys
nah I think we're good with the sword for those guys, so
I think I'm missing something I need here to complete the level
So we'll just, we'll do this... We'll do this some other time
Time to unleash hell
Yep let's do that
Back to the shadows
Uhn-uh uh, that's not the thing you do there
I was thinking I could because there was a,
I was thinking I could because there was, a secret area with
Some money but, I was a little off
Wrong door. Again.
There we go
Are we at another dead end
These symbols me nothing to me
I don't know if restarting. And quitting, do the same thing for our health or whatever.
Ain't no way there's a way to continue right now
I guess we'll go back to the hedge
I guess we'll go back to the hedge, the hedges
Did all that stuff
Oh that's the building we're seeing. The Asylum. That's the Asylum.
That's easy, that's an elephant
Kitties
Yeah, that's right; -eat- my arrows!
Weird bird octopus thing.
Bat.
And it kind of like a
it's like a... it's like a
it's like a... it's like a, cursed
Cthulhu Furby
[absurd laughter]
Weird Furby monster
Anything else in this area that I missed
Definitely not. Too small, not much not much to do there
I got the rune, let's head back
Doo
It is going to be a bit of a challenge with all these cats
Do I need to kill the cats?
Can I kill the cats?
I just avoid them
Oh dear
[laughs]
Keep this camera angle here
Yes that hides the blood too
What what do they call that game mechanic, in like Call of Duty
So many games use that
Nope no new path yet
Ooh I need that. Very badly.
How do I get there
Through the elephant
probably
I am gonna actually stick to ranged attacks here
I'm ready! Come get me.
Cowards
Oh my dear
Does that mean every one of them's defeated or is there still one alive back there
There's still a little bit of error
Room for error here.
You don't want to touch that chest.
Do not touch that chest.
Do not touch that chest. You will be dead.
Uh, wrong item
[fearful gasp]
I hit the explosive chest.
[sigh of relief]
Came within inches of my life being gone
ohhhh, we survived
ohhh, we survived :)
That is without a doubt the closest I've got
Closest I've got to dying for the longest amount of time. that was…
That was, uhh
Scary. that was scary. Mhm hmm.
Okay…
[mouth click]
What's this then?
All this then?
Clearly a puzzle.
Of which I have no arrows. I need to find a gargoyle.
Or not.
This is very unfair.
Listen, game… If there's one thing you can learn from Zelda,
it's to give me refills in my items that I actually need to complete the dungeon
I have no arrows.
For I was fearing for my life back there.
Maybe I don't use arrows. Maybe maybe there's
something else here.
Okay I could just jump over the fence that's there for, some reason
it's to block the blocks from getting out of the area.
Clearly
I was thinking we'd find a fire arrow puzzle
Maybe at some point. Not here though.
It is a good thing to keep in mind for any enemies
We might want to catch on fire, hehehe
I‒ I guess I was supposed to do that - oh, chess
Oi !
Ok,
We have time for one more level.
Okay so now we can enchant a shield as well
Just like I did with my sword, right?
I enchanted it, right? Wrong weapon.
Ok, so it's just a gold shield basically.
There's nothing magical about it eh.
I am getting an idea that The Enchanted Earth comes later on in the game, so let's go to the Asylum.
For right now.
I feel like we go back to The Enchanted Earth.
Nothing screams "End Of Game" content other than. Shadowy.
Demons beyond our comprehension. Right?
Absolute hell on Earth.
Now this is dead-end as dead-ends get
This is dead as dead-ends get.
Really nothing to do back there
This is a combat level huh
This is a combat level, isn't it
After we just did a puzzle-only level pretty much
To fight a bunch of stuff
Well, that was fun.
Well, that was fun. Let's go again!
Let's actually, refill our health
we will do much better if we have full health.
Let's just take out all the stops here, in order to succeed
The easiest one at this point would be The Sleeping Village.
For a fountain. yeah.
We return to where we started the stream at
Almost 4 hours ago.
I ought to be able to leave here right
Not how it works
And in that case we'll go to an easier level
At least a shorter level
Which one would that be then
Cemetary Hill
Not sure if, The Graveyard might give us the
A refill. Even though I was just there.
Alright time to party
Alright time to party - Thriller style
Let's wrap things up
Even though these zombies are not wrapped up in bandages.
Oh I should've enchanted my sword again
Let's yeah let's do that
There is the gargoyle here although we have to finish the level for it to count right
Back we go.
Back we go. That's so silly.
Back we go. That's so silly. I'm so silly.
I don't really think about this game
I am a novice.
I think a lot -of- this game. It's really good.
Bah! Copper shield.
Correct me if I'm wrong you couldn't repeal repair the Silver Shield right
Could you repair your shield before?
'cause those shields weren't given to us from The Hall of Heroes guys. Folk.
Yeah I'm not sure about that
Being a bit of a copycat here
Ooh fast zombies
We're kiting them over
One more to go. Assuming that's correct.
Might even be a boss
No room to run here though
And they're not stupid enough to walk into the lava
The coals there, like...
like...
I wouldn't say in unintelligent, they're more
Actually crazy.
Yike!
That's a thing that happens
I'll just stay over here and pick them off
Cool but the Chalice isn't full yet.
Cool but the Chalice isn't full yet. Oh yeah it is, okay.
Nice
I fell in the magma once
Fortunately
I got to refill again but that doesn't matter anyway
that doesn't matter because I am going to finish the stream now we are going to be complete
With our 4-Hour stream here
With our 4-Hour stream here, that we're gonna
I'm gonna get going here
Who are you.
Who are you. The Mad Hatter?
Actually yeah he probably is just the Mad Hatter innit he?
Thanks mayor
I'm sorry I thought you were a.
Mad Hatter, though. You do look very eccentric.
That everything then?
That everything then? Got the Chalice.
That everything then? Got the Chalice. A...
That everything then? Got the Chalice. A Dragon Gem.
Ooh.
I think I know what that's for just making a guess here.
Potentially.
Might just be for the shadow.
Shadow monsters
Yeah sure
I wasn't wrong about that - the more you have your sword out,
the more it loses its enchantment
I left it out while I was away and it just wasn't enchanted when I came back
Repair the Gold Sh‒ Yeah that's, good.
Alrighty
Yeah I think we need to go back to the enchanted forest I think that's what the Dragon Gem's for.
But I'm not going to do any, anymore of that level
I just want to see if it does anything.
Seems like we need four of something in order to do the shadow, tomb, demon place.
This was fun
I made a lot more progress
Than I thought I would in 4 hours... But, pretty good
Pre‒tty good.
Actually we have two paths in the forest, still, here
There appears to be two different ways we can go
Curious. Is...?
It would totally say if...
It would totally say if, I could use this here
It is not saying anything.
I'm not going to
I'm not going to, no healing.
I can't finish this level, right
Right. It is also a puzzle. It's a matter of order.
OK. I get it.
Cool.
Cool. I think. I think this is cool?
That doesn't seem like it
And now we must catch all the ghosts‒ I mean, destroy the Shadows right?
We didn't unleash any Luigi's Mansion-esque monsters upon us
This is much more serious than that
But I'm going to I'm going to call the stream
Call it here
Go ahead and
Gonna go ahead and click end because I don't really have any music tonight, and
I'd like to do a few things before I go to bed so
Get right to that. Thanks for watching.