Aphelion: The galactic map has been updated
with coordinates to the Vela Sector.
Thinking we don't have enough
time to do the next planet. So,
I guess we could do some side content
I don't have a boost yet.
Okay, just chill. Vibe.
Destroy this, satellite that's coming up
Aphelion: Sensors detect security satellites with holo-net relays.
They must be destroyed in order to
clear the sector of fighter patrols.
Satellite: Lombax identified. Alert Dr. Nefarious.
That's why you want to do this because
you get more bolts.
The ship is upgraded through the Zoni.
Which you also can find around
Space.
Satellite: Shields disengaged.
Summoning reinforcements.
Let's stop at a depot first.
And we'll do one or two moon... exploration.
>> Welcome back, chief.
>> Hi, doomguy.
We're just about to wrap up
playing Ratchet & Clank for tonight.
We'll be switching to Rayman 1.
Playing all the games on my PS3
tonight without any emulators.
There's a Zoni on this planet.
You do need them to progress through the game.
There there is a limit.
Once in a while, a few times throughout
the game where,
they'll tell you to get more Zoni.
We might as well get a head start on that. Yeah
Yeah, it's been forever since I've, played this game. It's been a long time coming for,
completing all the trophies.
I know we've done it on the channel, so
felt like it would be so disappointing
to not finish the Future games.
We'll be streaming next month, for this game
along with some other stuff I have planned.
Forgot to disable that reminder
Kingdom Hearts is tomorrow.
We be playing an hour or so of Kingdom Hearts.
Check the schedule below the
video player for more information.
Actually, uh, The Golden Bolt did a review
on this, uh, PS3 games. I think
he finished those actually. I recommend The Golden Bolt. Those are some really in-depth, uh, video essays.
Zoni
Oh, okay.
Yeah Into the Nexus really is part
of the Future, series of games
The whole uh plot about dimensions and
people being lost to other dimensions.
It it, it fits right in with the Future...
It's an epilogue. I believe that's how Insomniac called it.
I mean, really, we still haven't got a
conclusion on the Lombaxes yet.
Did I get a checkpoint?
Not that I've played the PS5 game yet. I,
I don't want any spoilers for that.
Too much content.
What kind of criticism is that? Yeah, I don't
want more I don't want as much gameplay.
Thanks, Insomniac. Just put less gameplay in your
games next time. What?
It has an arena. It has sh- space combat.
It has a lot of the stuff that was cut previous games.
It's It's a, an. it's a...
It's honestly a feat that they pulled it off.
The only way games could have
too much if its filler, you know,
but all the stuff in this game is fun, you
know? It's it's there. It has a purpose, and
gives the player more to do.
None of it is really filler.
stuff that would have been filler, they cut.
You know, like the Hoverboot races
probably were just not fleshed out enough,
they weren't developed enough to add them to the game.
The Hoverboots though are really fun.
Same thing with the uh, Ratchet & Clank 3
content
PS2. They, they were gonna to do space combat. They were gonna to do, racing ‒
But at the end of the day, they just didn't have enough time to put that in the game.
I think if you compare this to your Up Your Arsenal, there's so much more content.
They did a good job with...
Sly 4 isn't canon?
This guy hates the number four like Valve hates the number three or something.
Fifth or sixth time I've died
Yeah...
Isn't there like four Indiana Jones movies?
Would he say the same thing about a, fourth movie of that? Like—
I know. I know.
Pretty sure I know which movie I'm talking about:
Just because you don't like
the movie doesn't mean it's not canon
And I would guess he would say
Into the Nexus was too short, too.
Not every game—
Oh it's not canon either? Yeah...
It starts in the Starship Phoenix.
It starts with Sasha
becoming mayor of Metropolis.
Like that, that didn't happen??
Of cour‒  We haven't seen Sasha again,
but that doesn't mean it's not canon
Actually!
I believe that Sasha is mentioned
in the comics - as mayor, too.
And are those canon? They sure are. They're written by the same person who did the story for this game.
Yeah, I agree. I agree. Into the Nexus
needed like three more planets to be
as good as like Ratchet 1 or something, yeah.
Ratchet 1 has like 20 planets, but -
quantity, quality - yeah.
Alright, this looks like it'll be the
last thing we do in this game for tonight.
As soon as I stop dying. [laugh]
Yeah, a lot of people have vendettas
against Sly 4 probably. I would not be surprised.
Oh my god.
That wouldn't have happened if Clank was here.
I don't care. I'm here for the Zoni, buddy.
OK, OK. You can have a bomb if you want-
Okay.
I would say this is a shortcut, but I don't think it is.
Oh, it is. How handy. Okay.
Uh we'll save the game here.
Yeah, Golden Bolt is very in-depth.
Kevin. Yep.
Okay.
K', I'll take a few minute break.
Get the disc in for Rayman
Will be back
Power failure detected in auxiliary server room.