Warning. Hostile ships detected.
Point of origin appears to be the same as
Captain Qwark's nav-beacon.
Hello. Let's get back to
saving Qwark and the fongoids
and take a moment out to—
Ratchet:
Qwark, I'm at the ship. Where are they holding you?
Qwark: I don't know. It's a big cell with some sort of containment field, [sniff]
ugh, that smells like my high school gym locker.
>> Alright, maintain radio silence.
I'll contact you when I'm inside.
>> I had to take a moment to address the fact that it's really warm in here.
And I also need caffeine.
I've actually had coffee for a while I just haven't been,
even drinking it.
Got a coffee warmer. So, we're good. But,
I don't want any tiredness to set in now. We haven't even got to Rayman yet.
Which will be in,
an hour.
We are starting Rayman in an hour.
Less than an hour it look- hour. Round it up. Round it up.
Ship Computer:
Breach detected in starboard airlock.
Dispatching engineer.
Vorselon: Attention troopers. We have just
learned that the rebel Azimuth
has escaped our troops once again.
I have spoken with Dr. Nefarious and
he has agreed to raise the bounty
to 50,000 bolts. Dead or alive.
Enemy Trooper: I am an engineer, I fix stuff.
Nefarious doesn't want anyone else controlling the clock, he wants his‒
He wants him‒
it all to himself.
>> Trooper: Fred, is that you?
Trooper: Azimuth has escaped. You owe me five bolts.
Ship Computer:
Hyperspace fueling module, released.
Vorselon: Attention troopers: This is a reminder that no one is to execute the prisoners until we have extracted the
location of the rebel Azimuth.
Also, we will be serving fried weasel in the cafeteria.
>> Weasel?
...Cafeteria food is *not* very good.
Trooper: Ow, that hurts.
Sonic Eruptor detected.
Ship Computer: Containment grid disabled.
Ship Computer:
Unauthorized personnel in cargo substation seven.
Dispatching security team.
>> The rebel is here. The rebel is here. Alert. Alert.
Fresh off the assembly line at GrummelNet HQ.
Welcome to the GrummelNet weapon shop.
Yep, you get a discount if you played Tools of Destruction.
Save file for it.
Welcome back, chief.
You're full up, chief.
Trooper: The rebel is here. Alert. Alert.
Welcome back, chief.
Trooper: Destroy the rebel.
Got a holo-plan for the RYNO V.
Ratchet:
Qwark, give me a status update.
Qwark: This guy Vorselon means business.
He says he'll kill us if we don't
give up Alister Azimuth.
>> Who is Alister Azimuth?
>> I don't know, some rebel.
>> Alright, well find out what you can. If he's an enemy of Nefarious, he might be a friend to us.
By the way, the pizza I had earlier was cauliflower crust pizza.
Tasty. A bit done though.
Wrong weapon.
Trying to level everything up to be three at the moment.
Coffee. Coffee! I feel I feel... I feel my eyelids
getting somewhat heavy. So, not, not a good sign.
[Music]
That's something you you can't get rid of.
Oh yeah, there's supposed to be a teaser
trailer for the The Super Mario Bros. Movie.
[Music]
I'm just so curious to see, what kind of uh.
How much uh the characters talk, I guess. You know.
What kind of style they go with. Is it going
to be like wacky, happy-go-lucky sort of,
Minions stuff. Or are they going to be somewhat like
Luigi's Mansion 3 and those those cutscenes.
Top level cutcenes. I'm I'm gonna play Luigi's Mansion 3,
I swear. I'm going to beat it this year for Halloween.
Probably not play the original Luigi's Mansion.
There goes the burp. Good.
I have nothing else to talk about. [laugh] Really.
I go in the right room...? No I'm not.
I know I'm not going the right direction.
The second or the third time I've died
Yeah I died to this guy previously, on the, uh -
Quantos
- That planet.
Live streams are really a different tone compared to let's plays.
Trying to think how would I even let's play this game and not
Have dead air.
I don't know, hah
I guess I did it with A Cra‒, Tools of Destruction, and uh
Quest for Booty, didn't I?
Guess I edited it out
Ship Computer:
Secondary hyperspace fueling module, released.
>> I always think the gameplay should be, uh
Shouldn't miss anything, with a let's play.
Ship Computer:
Um... Third-iary hyperspace fueling module, released.
>> It's 'tertiary' computer voice. Tertiary.
You need to upgrade your AI
It- It's, uh
Ship Computer:
Power failure detected in auxillary server room.
>> You're... You're serving weasles
at your cafeteria, I don't know. It's a little weird.
Vorselon:
Attention troopers:
>> Maybe weasles are really good if they're space weasles.
Vorselon:
I don't want to point fingers,
>> Maybe weasles are really good if they're space weasles.
Vorselon:
But SOMEONE taped over last night's episode of Lance and Janice.
>> Get these
Vorselon:
But SOMEONE taped over last night's episode of Lance and Janice.
>> All turned around
Vorselon:
Will the trooper responsible please eject yourself out the airlock immediately.
Thank you.
>> The work environment sounds... lovely
Lovely.
I think the last time "Lance and Janice" was mentioned was Deadlocked, I believe -
Ship Computer:
What floor, please?
>> going back.
Ratchet: Um,
Ratchet:
Detention wing?
Wow. I can't believe that worked.
Ship Computer:
What was that?
Ratchet:
...Nothing!
Vorselon:
Insolent creature!
Give me the location of the rebel Azimuth!
Fongoid:
We don't know!!
That wasn't Azimuth, it was just a young lombax!
Vorselon:
You are foolish to protect him.
Guards! Throw them in the brig.
If they haven't broken by the time we jump sectors,
eject them out the airlock!
Fongoid:
Someone! Help us!
>> Guy doesn't know who Azimuth is
Shake my head,
shake my head.
A lot older than that, pfft. C'mon.
Snoop around chief. You've got a right to
You have a vague idea of who he is maybe
Nefarious knows who he is, maybe he just, like...
Qwark:
We did it!
Everyone follow me! I'll get us outta here.
Ratchet: Stay quiet. We don't want to set off the alarm.
Ship Computer:
Alert! Alert!
There is a code red in the detention wing.
Repeat - code red in the detention wing.
Mobilize all units.
Trooper: They must not leave the ship
Trooper: Alert Lord Vorselon.
Qwark:
Alright, let's go. Remember the buddy system.
Having Qwark actually do something in this game;
Not gonna lie, that's kind of, uh
>> Qwark: The bridge is out— It's out!
Captain Qwark: What do we do?!
>> meaningful.
Has he ever done anything to help Ratchet,
in gameplay, huh?
I mean, I guess hitting him when he's was a monkey -
kinda funny, but doesn't really do anything of value.
Comic relief
Explosive?
Blew it up
Nope, don't need anything.
Qwark:
We did it!
Everyone follow me! I'll get us outta here.
Ratchet: Stay quiet. We don't want to set off the alarm.
Ship Computer:
Alert! Alert!
There is a code red in the detention wing.
>> Trooper: They are escaping.
Repeat - code red in the detention wing.
Mobilize all units.
Qwark:
Alright, let's go. Remember the buddy system.
Taunting me
with bolts
Qwark: The bridge is out— It's out!
What do we do?!
>> Throw the little one across it. Heh.
Trooper: Hey! Get your own prisoners.
Qwark: Ahem, yes — well, well done! Ha,
>> Oh no a big one again
Qwark: I almost had to hurl you all to safety myself.
>> Here goes nothin'!
Am I gonna die?
...Stand behind Qwark?
I don't want to risk it.
This barrier
I'm tempting fate by saying that
Ugh!
You keep shooting at the ground - it might help...
>> Trooper: The fongoids are free.
Vorselon: They're heading for the escape vessel.
Shut down the auto launch module.
Stop- Mmm,
The quick select pause - I'm keeping it.
Regardless of how many times I die
It's just less annoying, I think, as a viewer
This pistol is a no-thought weapon
>> Trooper: Lock down the detention wing.
Until you run out of ammo I guess
Mr. Zurkon: One little, two little dead little toasters.
Four little, five little dead little toasters.
>> Clank was a toaster...
Clank was a toaster... [sad whimper]
He's not dead though. He's alive.
'K
Is that it? Except for the,
Oh- it was nothing.
I, I don't know if you can even come back through here
I haven't seen any gold bolts yet, so
Nothing hidden
I love bolt cranks, it lets me.
Give a chance to look away from the game
>> Hello, bolt crank??
Clearly... I've never seen a bolt crank not work before.
>> Okay. I'm missing something.
Whew!
Qwark. What do I do here?
Qwark. What do I do here? Oh that.
Oh that's just for collectables.
Oh you release them first.
>> Systematic nonsense
Okay that opens the door
I guess that jettisons the cargo, uh the the
Excess car— and the,
>> Qwark: The onboard computer says
Qwark:
there's a manual switch somewhere in that room -
Check the grav-ramp.
>> the escape pod.
Vorselon: Nooo!
Vorselon:
Computer, perform a bioscan across the entire ship.
I want to know who helped those creatures escape!
Ship Computer:
Bioscan indicates one Lombax lifeform.
Vorselon: Azimuth! Welcome back.
Vorselon:
I kept your old cell warm in the event you ever returned.
Vorselon: Computer, ready my best mech suit.
I'll handle this personally.
>> You're a little blobby guy just sitting there
at his console. In his fish tank, talkin' trash
Out of the mech suit
Suit‒ it's gotta, it's gotta
conserve power to kill people, I guess
>> Aphelion, they've blocked my escape route. Meet me in the lower deck landing bay.
>> Affirmative. ETA: In 30 seconds.
Be with you shortly—
I'm gonna break some stuff
One bolt? C'mon.
Happy to meet you.
Here's a bomb.
Guess this area opens up some more
So if we do come back
>> Is your ar‒
Alright chief, what can we do you for?
Full.
>> —Arsenal antiquated? Your firepower fossilized?
—Arsenal antiquated? Your firepower fossilized?
>> Vendor.
Don't be embarrassed on the battlefield with last year's weapon.
In a very important location
Yep, this looks like a boss arena.
>> I guess his armor's pretty cool
Let's see how his boss fight fairs
Vorselon: Amateur! Did you really expect that
to work? You'd think we'd never done dance this before.
Vorselon: Is that it? Is that everything!?
>> Evidentally,
>> Azimuth actually meddled with Dr. Nefarious before
'cause he doesn't know who Ratchet is.
Guess they're both after the Clock, but
I thought that plot only started in this game
time-wise
Vorselon: You are messing with Lord Vorselon!
Not even could Zordoom Prison could hold me!
Vorselon: Rgah! You're slower than last time, Azimuth.
You wouldn't be taking it easy on Lord Vorselon, would you?
I should have killed you back on Lumos!
>> Krell Canyon, innit
Vorselon: Now you don't!
>> Sneaky, sneaky
[where you gonna] Stop!
Vorselon: Lucky shot!
Vorselon: Ohh, how I've waited for this.
>> That's annoying
This fight gives you ammo though, right?
Vorselon: No, I will not allow it!
I will not be beaten by some worthless has-been!
>> I don't think you know who you're talking to,
this guy's saved two galaxies
>> Vorselon: You're supposed to be the strongest of your kind.
Vorselon: You're supposed to be the strongest of your kind.
>> Three galaxies, including this one.
Vorselon: What happened?
Vorselon: Did you stop caring?
Or did your mind finally just snap?
Brah ha ha ha haha haa!
This cannot be happening!
Lord Vorselon will not fall to this terrible creature!
>> Now I need ammo
I like your death ray, it reminds me of Dr. Nefarious'
only less purple and less, awesome.
>> Vorselon: [sneakily]  Heh, heh, heh heh heh.
Don't like it as much.
It's very... Reminiscent. For that it gets some points.
Oh I almost got hit!
>> Lord Vorselon: How is this possible?!
>> "This can't be happening!"
Qwark:
Ratchet, great news. The Chief says Alister
Azimuth lives on Torren IV in the Vela Sector.
I'm uploading coordinates to your ship now.
In the meantime, I'll stay with the fongoids and find out what else they know about Azimuth. Qwark out.
>> I gotta get some ammo because I don't have to die at all
That's what I wanted to do, but,
No boxes?
Last time I was here,
Last time I was here, there were boxes.
Last time I played, there were boxes respawning
over and over. Ah. Ok. Alright, game.
Maybe that was just a bug.
'K
Maybe, are we full up on ammo, eh. I'm far from it.
Trooper: [over radio]
Sir, one of the prisoners has requested to speak with you.
He appears to be willing to cooperate.
Vorselon: Patch it through.
Qwark: Uhh, hey, Mr. Vorselon? Uh, my name's Captain Qwark, maybe you've heard of me?
"Saviour of Solana"? Number 97 in "Kerwan's 100 Most Eligible Bachelors", ha ha.
[breathes in] Anyway— uh, you seem like a reasonable...
floating, head in a tank, so,
I was wondering if we could settle this without violence?
Vorselon: Insolent creature!
Your request has fallen on deaf ears.
The only future you may hope for
is a quick and merciful death,
following hours of unimaginable agony.
Qwark: Huh. So that's a "No", right?